<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<xml>
  <help id="terms_and_conditions">
    <title>Terms and conditions</title>
    <![CDATA[The following Terms and Conditions are valid from May 25th 2005.
<br><br>
The information posted on this website are compiled by Reykjavik Marathon and are not by any means guaranteed to be accurate or exhaustive.  The information may furthermore be imperfect, i.e. they may include aberrations, faults and etc., and may be out-of-date.  Therefore it would be prudent to verify the information at the offices of Reykjavik Marathon before any arrangements are made that are based on them.
<br><br><br>
I.  GENERAL TERMS
<br><br>
1.      The following Terms apply to the payment of the entry fee from the participant to Reykjavik Marathon.  By signing up, and paying an entry-fee for an event held by Reykjavik Marathon, the participant agrees to defer to the Terms.
<br><br>
2.      Reykjavik Marathon is not responsible for the health of participants in any of its events, neither during nor after.
<br><br>
3.      If a participant has signed up for an event at marathon.is he can only deactivate his registration by contacting the offices of Reykjavik Marathon or send an e-mail, containing the request for deactivation, to <a href="mailto:marathon@marathon.is">marathon@marathon.is</a>.
<br><br>
4.      It is admissible for Reykjavik Marathon to update or alter these Terms at any time without any notice of any kind.  By agreeing to defer to these Terms the participant accepts to be bound by any changes.
<br><br>
5.      The participant agrees to give Reykjavik Marathon full and unrestricted access, without any compensation, to all his personal information sent to Reykjavik Marathon via the registration website, under the notice that those information are to be used for marketing research and etc.
<br><br>
6.      All trade names, brands, logos and etc., that are posted on the Reykjavik Marathon website are protected by icelandic and international law.  Any use of any such object are prohibited without the prior written approval by Reykjavik Marathon.
<br><br>
7.      Reykjavik Marathon does not guarantee the contents of any websites which may be linked to the Reykjavik Marathon website.  Reykjavik Marathon does not have any say over topics, subjects or the setup of any websites other than its own.
<br><br><br>
II.  TERMS OF PAYMENT
<br><br>
8.      On the website there is a calculator which will provide the participant with the entry fee he will be asked to pay.  The entry fee will be provided in Euros.  If a participant is to pay for multiple participants the calculator will reveal the total entry fee.
<br><br>
9.     No taxes will be added to the provided entry fee.
<br><br>
10.     If an event does not go ahead as planned, due to natural catastrophies, adverse weather conditions etc., the entry fee will not be repaid.
<br><br>
11.     If a participant already owns a ChampionsChip the calculator includes a discount option for the entry fee for the Midnight Run or the Reykjavik Marathon.  No discount will be given in connection with the Ultra Marathon (Laugavegur).
<br><br>
12.     Every participant is responsible for the payment of the entry fee to Reykjavik Marathon, independent of whether he turns up for the event in question or not.  The participant shall however be entitled to receive all complementary goods, to be dispersed to participants of the event. 
<br><br>
13.     Registration for an event is not possible without the previous payment of the required entry fees.]]>
  </help>
</xml>

